The key improvement was in the
models.  Again, I might have heard
of post-training, of reinforce
and learning.  There are new techniques, but
especially we have understood how
to use much more compute in this
post-training phase which makes the
models not only powerful in generating
code, but also able to understand the
series of actions that must be performed to
obtain a certain result.  Essentially, they
start behaving similarly
to a software engineer, perhaps not a
principal level, a person who has been in the
business for 30 years.  Although we're
getting there pretty quickly.  This
unlock has been happening literally since
December of last year.  The new
version of Opus,
Antropic's flagship model, was another
major feature improvement over
what we'd seen in the
previous year, and suddenly all agents
using that model became
much more powerful.  For that reason, it has
also seen many companies grow in
terms of revenue,
number of customers, and adoption.
Everything was key on these models
that became better.  We're
doing this extreme focus on people
who aren't technical, but who are able
to build very advanced software.
Now I have a long list of companies that
rebuild maybe software that
they bought for hundreds of thousands of
dollars with 10,000 on repliit.